<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://webhosts.cr.usgs.gov/mod/FGDC_Plus.xsl"?>-->
<!DOCTYPE metadata SYSTEM "http://thor-f5.er.usgs.gov/ngtoc/metadata/fgdc-std-001-1998.dtd">
<metadata>
  <idinfo>
    <citation>
      <citeinfo>
        <origin>U.S. Geological Survey</origin>
        <pubdate>20110926</pubdate>
        <title>USGS US Topo 7.5-minute map for Toano, VA 2011</title>
        <geoform>map, raster digital data</geoform>
        <pubinfo>
          <pubplace>Rolla, MO and Denver, CO</pubplace>
          <publish>USGS - National Geospatial Technical Operations Center (NGTOC)</publish>
        </pubinfo>
        <onlink>https://prd-tnm.s3.amazonaws.com/StagedProducts/Maps/USTopo/1/13057/4703349.pdf</onlink>
        <lworkcit>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>U.S. Geological Survey</origin>
            <pubdate>2015</pubdate>
            <title>US Topo Historical</title>
            <onlink>https://www.sciencebase.gov/catalog/item/5061bc99e4b0ce47085a8d03</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </lworkcit>
      </citeinfo>
    </citation>
    <descript>
      <abstract>Layered GeoPDF 7.5 Minute Quadrangle Map. Layers of geospatial data include orthoimagery, roads, grids, geographic names, elevation contours, hydrography, and other selected map features.</abstract>
      <purpose>This map depicts geographic features on the surface of the earth. It is a general purpose map for users who are not GIS experts. One intended purpose is to support emergency response at all levels of government. The geospatial data in this map are from selected National Map data holdings and other government sources.</purpose>
      <supplinf>{"gdaId" : 5466529, "cellId" : 45267, "scale" : 24000, "pageWidth" : 22.75, "pageHeight" : 29}</supplinf>
    </descript>
    <timeperd>
      <timeinfo>
        <rngdates>
          <begdate>1972</begdate>
          <enddate>2010</enddate>
        </rngdates>
      </timeinfo>
      <current>publication date</current>
    </timeperd>
    <status>
      <progress>Complete</progress>
      <update>Irregular</update>
    </status>
    <spdom>
      <bounding>
        <westbc>-76.875</westbc>
        <eastbc>-76.75</eastbc>
        <northbc>37.5</northbc>
        <southbc>37.375</southbc>
      </bounding>
    </spdom>
    <keywords>
      <theme>
        <themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt>
        <themekey>imageryBaseMapsEarthCover</themekey>
        <themekey>EarthCover</themekey>
        <themekey>Imagery and Base Maps</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>None</themekt>
        <themekey>topographic</themekey>
        <themekey>transportation</themekey>
        <themekey>structures</themekey>
        <themekey>geographic names</themekey>
        <themekey>hydrography</themekey>
        <themekey>orthoimage</themekey>
        <themekey>contour</themekey>
        <themekey>U.S. National Grid</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>The National Map Type Thesaurus</themekt>
        <themekey>Downloadable Data</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>The National Map Theme Thesaurus</themekt>
        <themekey>Map</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>The National Map Collection Thesaurus</themekt>
        <themekey>US Topo Historical</themekey>
        <themekey>US Topo</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>The National Map Product Extent Thesaurus</themekt>
        <themekey>7.5 x 7.5 minute</themekey>
      </theme>
      <theme>
        <themekt>The National Map Product Format Thesaurus</themekt>
        <themekey>GeoPDF</themekey>
      </theme>
      <place>
        <placekt>Geographic Names Information System</placekt>
        <placekey>US</placekey>
        <placekey>United States</placekey>
        <placekey>Virginia</placekey>
        <placekey>James City</placekey>
        <placekey>New Kent</placekey>
        <placekey>King and Queen</placekey>
      </place>
      <place>
        <placekt>None</placekt>
        <placekey>Toano, VA</placekey>
      </place>
    </keywords>
    <accconst>None</accconst>
    <useconst>None. However, users should be aware that temporal changes may have occurred since this data set was collected and that some parts of this data may no longer represent actual surface conditions. Users should not use this data for critical applications without a full awareness of its limitations. Acknowledgment of the U.S. Geological Survey would be appreciated for products derived from these data.</useconst>
    <browse>
      <browsen>https://prd-tnm.s3.amazonaws.com/StagedProducts/Maps/USTopo/1/13057/4703350.jpg</browsen>
      <browsed>Thumbnail JPG image of map</browsed>
      <browset>JPEG</browset>
    </browse>
  </idinfo>
  <dataqual>
    <attracc>
      <attraccr>Cartographic content is derived from USGS national geospatial databases. The data is owned and hosted by the USGS, but does not preclude using data sources owned and hosted by other organizations, provided that these sources have been approved by the USGS data program.</attraccr>
    </attracc>
    <logic>This product is a layered GeoPDF file. GeoPDF is a copyright format with implementation rights held exclusively by TerraGo Technologies. This design is based on use of specific commercial software systems therefore any changes to the software specifications and dependencies will be followed by the USGS and codified in the product standard.</logic>
    <complete>Each layer of the GeoPDF is extracted from the USGS national geospatial databases. These data are intended to be cartographically complete at a 1:24,000 scale.</complete>
    <posacc>
      <horizpa>
        <horizpar>This US Topo map product is compiled to meet National Map Accuracy Standards (NMAS). NMAS horizontal accuracy requires that at least 90 percent of well-defined points tested are within 0.02 inch of the true position. In this product, the projection line, grids, and orthoimage are believed to meet NMAS. Positional accuracy of the other data layers is less controllable because of diversity of data sources, and may not meet NMAS.</horizpar>
      </horizpa>
      <vertacc>
        <vertaccr>The accuracy of the National Elevation Dataset (NED) is inherited from the source digital elevation models (DEMs). The overall absolute vertical accuracy expressed as the root mean square error (RMSE) is 2.44 meters. The measured vertical RMSE was converted to equivalent NMAS and NSSDA expressions. The accuracy is expressed in terms of the National Map Accuracy Standards (NMAS), which use a 90 percent confidence interval, and in terms of the National Standard for Spatial Data Accuracy (NSSDA), which uses a 95 percent confidence interval. </vertaccr>
      </vertacc>
    </posacc>
    <lineage>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>National Agriculture Image Program (NAIP) administered by the Aerial Photography Field Office (APFO) for the United States Department of Agriculture. </origin>
            <pubdate>20090629</pubdate>
            <title>Orthoimagery</title>
            <geoform>Raster digital data or Digital Orthorectified Image or NAIP Digital Ortho Photo Image</geoform>
            <othercit>An orthorectified image is a layer in every product and is provided by the USDA-FSA-APFO from the National Agriculture Image Program (NAIP). This offers the USGS a nationally consistent image product, normally with a one meter resolution in natural color.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://www.fsa.usda.gov/</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>20090629</begdate>
              <enddate>20090629</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Imagery</srccitea>
        <srccontr>Image</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>Tele Atlas</origin>
            <pubdate>2010</pubdate>
            <title>Transportation, commercial roads</title>
            <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            <othercit>Tele Atlas Multinet dataset, licensed to the USGS for use in US Topo (1:24,000-scale topographic maps in GeoPDF format). Tele Atlas retains copyright to these data. The USGS license allows these data to be freely used and redistributed in US Topo instances, provided this copyright notice is retained. Tele Atlas data are filtered and may be generalized by USGS for protrayal in this product. Tele Atlas roads are not mixed with other road data sources within a 7.5-minute quadrangle, with the exception of U.S. Forest Service lands, where public domain data from the Forest Service are used.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://www.teleatlas.com/</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>2006</begdate>
              <enddate>2010</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Roads - Tele Atlas</srccitea>
        <srccontr>Road centerlines, route numbers, road classification, street names</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>Federal Aviation Administration</origin>
            <pubdate>2010</pubdate>
            <title>Airports</title>
            <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            <othercit>Runway outlines are for Federal Aviation Administration (FAA)-recognized public and private airports in the United States. The 2008 FAA runway coordinates, FAA_RunwayID, and Airport Location Codes were used by the USGS to digitize runway outlines on recent NAIP orthoimagery. The digitized data were inspected for accuracy and completeness then loaded into the USGS national transportation database.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://www.faa.gov</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>2008</begdate>
              <enddate>2010</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Transportation - Airports</srccitea>
        <srccontr>runways</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>U.S. Geological Survey</origin>
            <pubdate>2010</pubdate>
            <title>Geographic Names Information System (GNIS)</title>
            <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            <othercit>The National Geographic Names Database is a part of the Geographic Names Information System (GNIS) and represents the primary source for identifying official names. The system is maintained by the U.S. Geological Survey in cooperation with the U.S. Board of Geographic Names.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://geonames.usgs.gov/</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>2010</begdate>
              <enddate>2010</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Geographic Names</srccitea>
        <srccontr>Geographic feature names</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>U.S. Geological Survey in cooperation with U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, USDA Forest Service, and other Federal, State and local partners. National Hydrography Dataset is a component of a comprehensive base geospatial data model.</origin>
            <pubdate>20090629</pubdate>
            <title>Hydrography</title>
            <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            <othercit>The National Hydrography Dataset (NHD) is a feature-based database that interconnects and uniquely identifies the stream segments or reaches that make up the nation's surface water drainage system. The high-resolution NHD was originally created using 1:24,000-scale data. State and Local Stewards are improving the data by incorporating local updates based on more current and more accurate source data. Water features in the real world are relatively dynamic and the differences at the time of data collection mean that water features may not register exactly to other layers. The hydrographic feature names contained in and displayed by the NHD are extracted and validated from the Geographic Names Information System (GNIS).</othercit>
            <onlink>http://nhd.usgs.gov/</onlink>
            <onlink>http://nhd.usgs.gov/gnis.html</onlink>
            <onlink>http://nhdgeo.usgs.gov/metadata/nhd_high.htm</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>20090629</begdate>
              <enddate>20090629</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Hydrography</srccitea>
        <srccontr>Hydrography features and feature names</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>International Boundary Commission</origin>
            <pubdate>2006</pubdate>
            <title>U.S.-Canada National Boundary</title>
            <othercit>The international boundary dataset between Canada and the United States was provided by Maine Office of Geographic Information Systems (MEGIS), University of New Hampshire, Vermont Center for Geographic Information, Inc (VCGI). The dataset was collected from multiple source agencies such as the U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Census, Bureau of Parks and Lands, Coastal Island Registry (CIREG) and various state agencies. The data and attribution accuracy was tested by manual comparison of the source with hard copy printouts and/or symbolized display of digital files and corrected by each state GIS department for use at a scale not greater than 1:24,000.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://www.internationalboundarycommission.org/</onlink>
            <onlink>http://www.internationalboundarycommission.org/products.html#nad83</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <typesrc>point digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>2006</begdate>
              <enddate>2006</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>U.S. / Canada International Boundary</srccitea>
        <srccontr>International Boundary between Canada and the United States</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Department of Agriculture, and the Instituto Nacional de Estadística y Geografía of Mexico.</origin>
            <pubdate>2006</pubdate>
            <title>U.S.-Mexico National Boundary</title>
            <othercit>The international boundary between Mexico and the United States, defined as a joint venture between the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) and the Instituto Nacional de Estadística y Geografía of Mexico (INEGI), resulted in an unofficial United States-Mexico boundary dataset that was further enhanced by the U.S. Geological Survey's Border Environmental Health Initiative (BEHI). With the data frame scale set to 1:5,000 in ArcMap, the center of the Rio Grande/Río Bravo was digitized using the NAIP 2004 Imagery. In areas with dense stands of salt cedar (bounding box = UL -104.714 30.038, UR -104.664 30.037, LR -104.666 29.933, LL -104.717 29.934; NAD83), the center of the channel was difficult, and sometimes impossible, to easily determine. To determine the location of the boundary, the GIS analyst compared the location of the line in the INEGI 1:250K Limite feature class with the NAIP 2004 Imagery and adjusted the boundary to the image, thus, the delineation of the international boundary is less certain in these areas. The remaining part of the border was extracted from the INEGI 1:250K Limite feature class and appended to the line feature class created along the Rio Grande/Río Bravo. The U.S. Geological Survey reviewed the original USDA data against 2007 NAIP imagery and further edited 9 line segments in the Rio Grande areas to conform to National Map Accuracy Standards.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://borderhealth.cr.usgs.gov/projectindex.html</onlink>
            <onlink>http://extract.cr.usgs.gov/BorderHealth/Boundaries/Int_Boundary/International_Boundary_Shapefile.zip</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <typesrc>vector digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>1972</begdate>
              <enddate>2006</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>U.S. / Mexico International Boundary</srccitea>
        <srccontr>International Boundary between Mexico and the United States</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>USGS - National Elevation Dataset is a component of a comprehensive base geospatial data model.</origin>
            <pubdate>19990413</pubdate>
            <title>Hypsography</title>
            <geoform>Vector digital data</geoform>
            <othercit>This contour featureclass was generated from the 1/3 arc-second version of the National Elevation Dataset (NED). The intended viewing scale for these features is 1:24,000. The contours are derived from a filtered elevation raster to achieve smoother arcs. The NED data were modified by the National Hydrography Dataset (NHD) flow lines and water bodies to facilitate improved integration between the hypsography and hydrography on USGS map products. These contours were generated primarily for use as a layer in GeoPDFs created in the US Topo digital mapping program. The raster data source of contours is the National Elevation Dataset (NED) 1/3 arc-second layer. The 1/3 arc-second NED contains resampled data from the 1/9 arc-second layer of NED. Secondary datasets include the high resolution flow lines, water bodies, and areas from the National Hydrography Dataset (NHD). The NHD layers are used in hydro-enforcement of the DEM prior to contour generation. The goals of the hydro-enforcement are to prevent contour lines from extending over the surface of water bodies and to align the contour reentrants with the NHD single-line streams. The NED raster cells are converted to points. Those points, along with the NHD flow lines are input into an interpolation tool to create a new surface. The NHD water bodies and areas are preprocessed to attach the minimum and maximum elevation to each polygon. From these precalculated values, an appropriate value is calculated by which to raise the elevation cells under the NHD polygons. The NHD polygons are then converted into rasters, which in turn will be used to generate a mosaic that includes the new raster surface. The mosaic is filtered to provide smoother contour lines. Contours are generated and depression and index contours are identified. There is no guarantee or warranty concerning the accuracy of the data. Users should be aware that temporal changes may have occurred since these data were collected and generated and that some parts of these data may no longer represent actual surface conditions. Hydro-enforcement and generalization can also significantly alter the spatial characteristics of the contours. Users should not use these data for critical applications without a full awareness of its limitations.</othercit>
            <onlink>http://ned.usgs.gov/</onlink>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <srcscale>24000</srcscale>
        <typesrc>digital data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>19990413</begdate>
              <enddate>19990413</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Hypsography</srccitea>
        <srccontr>Contours</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <srcinfo>
        <srccite>
          <citeinfo>
            <origin>U.S. Geological Survey</origin>
            <pubdate>Not Applicable</pubdate>
            <title>Grids and Coordinate System</title>
            <othercit>U.S. National Grid, UTM grid, and State Plane Coordinate System values are displayed along the map projection.</othercit>
          </citeinfo>
        </srccite>
        <typesrc>raster data</typesrc>
        <srctime>
          <timeinfo>
            <rngdates>
              <begdate>Not Applicable</begdate>
              <enddate>Not Applicable</enddate>
            </rngdates>
          </timeinfo>
          <srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
        </srctime>
        <srccitea>Grids and Coordinate Systems</srccitea>
        <srccontr>2.5-minute geographic ticks, U.S. National Grid, UTM grid, State Plane Coordinate System ticks.</srccontr>
      </srcinfo>
      <procstep>
        <procdesc>The GeoPDFs for this product are created as follows. All geospatial content is taken from national geospatial databases under the stewardship of USGS data programs. The NAIP imagery is provided by a seamless tile service that delivers image data at the resolution and quality of the source imagery. The raster and vector data, including grids and collar information, are processed using ESRI ArcGIS software and exported as a GeoPDF using the TerraGo ArcGIS software extension. Map formatting is performed using a custom application, which includes post-processing to embed the metadata XML document. GeoPDF is a copyrighted format, with implementation rights held exclusively by TerraGo Technologies. Any use of trade, product, or firm names in this publication is for descriptive purposes only and does not imply endorsement by the U.S. Government.</procdesc>
        <procdate>20110926</procdate>
      </procstep>
    </lineage>
  </dataqual>
  <spdoinfo>
    <direct>Raster</direct>
  </spdoinfo>
  <spref>
    <horizsys>
      <planar>
        <gridsys>
          <gridsysn>Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn>
          <utm>
            <utmzone>18</utmzone>
            <transmer>
              <sfctrmer>0.9996</sfctrmer>
              <longcm>-75</longcm>
              <latprjo>0.0</latprjo>
              <feast>500000</feast>
              <fnorth>0.0</fnorth>
            </transmer>
          </utm>
        </gridsys>
        <planci>
          <plance>coordinate pair</plance>
          <coordrep>
            <absres>2</absres>
            <ordres>2</ordres>
          </coordrep>
          <plandu>meters</plandu>
        </planci>
      </planar>
      <geodetic>
        <horizdn>North American Datum of 1983</horizdn>
        <ellips>Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips>
        <semiaxis>6378137</semiaxis>
        <denflat>298.2572221</denflat>
      </geodetic>
    </horizsys>
    <vertdef>
      <altsys>
        <altdatum>North American Vertical Datum of 1988</altdatum>
        <altres>3</altres>
        <altunits>meters</altunits>
        <altenc>Explicit elevation coordinate included with horizontal coordinates</altenc>
      </altsys>
    </vertdef>
  </spref>
  <eainfo>
    <overview>
      <eaover>This is a general-purpose design and layout quadrangle map based on the traditional USGS quadrangle cells. The domain is a standard 7.5-minute cell. The scale is 1:24,000.</eaover>
      <eadetcit>U.S. Department of the Interior, Draft US Topo Product Standard, Version 0.5.10.</eadetcit>
    </overview>
  </eainfo>
  <distinfo>
    <distrib>
      <cntinfo>
        <cntorgp>
          <cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey</cntorg>
        </cntorgp>
        <cntaddr>
          <addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
          <address>Box 25046 Denver Federal Center</address>
          <city>Lakewood</city>
          <state>CO</state>
          <postal>80225</postal>
        </cntaddr>
        <cntvoice>1-888-ASK-USGS (1-888-275-8747)</cntvoice>
        <cntemail>usgsstore@usgs.gov</cntemail>
      </cntinfo>
    </distrib>
    <resdesc>Downloadable Data</resdesc>
    <distliab>Although these data have been processed successfully on a computer system at the U.S. Geological Survey, no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the accuracy or utility of the data on any other system or for general or scientific purposes, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty. This disclaimer applies both to individual use of the data and aggregate use with other data. It is strongly recommended that these data are directly acquired from a U.S. Geological Survey server, and not indirectly through other sources which may have changed the data in some way. It is also strongly recommended that careful attention be paid to the contents of the metadata file associated with these data. The U.S. Geological Survey shall not be held liable for improper or incorrect use of the data described and/or contained herein.</distliab>
    <stdorder>
      <digform>
        <digtinfo>
          <formname>GeoPDF</formname>
          <transize>26.87452</transize>
        </digtinfo>
        <digtopt>
          <onlinopt>
            <computer>
              <networka>
                <networkr>https://prd-tnm.s3.amazonaws.com/StagedProducts/Maps/USTopo/1/13057/4703349.pdf</networkr>
              </networka>
            </computer>
          </onlinopt>
        </digtopt>
      </digform>
      <fees>None</fees>
    </stdorder>
  </distinfo>
  <metainfo>
    <metd>20160107</metd>
    <metc>
      <cntinfo>
        <cntorgp>
          <cntorg>U.S. Geological Survey, National Geospatial Technical Operations Center</cntorg>
        </cntorgp>
        <cntaddr>
          <addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
          <address>1400 Independence Road</address>
          <city>Rolla</city>
          <state>MO</state>
          <postal>6540HTTP/1.1 408 Request Timeout
Connection: Close
Content-Type: text/html

The requested service has timeout.<!--0123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234-->
r, at http://earthexplorer.usgs.gov or Ask USGS at http://www.usgs.gov/ask.</cntinst>
      </cntinfo>
    </metc>
    <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
    <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
  </metainfo>
</metadata>
